import { QuestionsInterface, CategoryInterface } from "../../interface/redux";
export const questionsArr: QuestionsInterface[] = [
  {
    question: `Which author wrote 'Coraline'?`,
    answer: "Neil Gaiman",
    options: [
      "Neil Gaiman",
      "Stephen King",
      "H. P. Lovecraft",
      "Douglas Adams",
    ],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `What is the nickname of the English football team Preston North End?`,
    answer: "The Lilywhites",
    options: ["The Lilywhites", "The Blades", "The Blues", "Douglas Adams"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which pasta's name means 'to hollow'?`,
    answer: "Cavatelli",
    options: ["Rotelle", "Cavatelli", "Vermicelli", "Pappardelle"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which president signed the Civil Rights Act of 1964??`,
    answer: "Lyndon B. Johnson",
    options: [
      "John F. Kennedy",
      "Lyndon B. Johnson",
      "Richard Nixon",
      "Jimmy Carter",
    ],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which of these countries borders Andorra?`,
    answer: "France",
    options: ["France", "Monaco", "Switzerland", "Luxembourg"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which of these brands has a eagle on its logo?`,
    answer: "Giorgio Armani",
    options: ["Giorgio Armani", "Lacoste", "Tripadvisor", "Bacardi"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which US state is divided into two parts by a large lake?`,
    answer: "Michigan",
    options: ["Michigan", "Ohio", "Minnesota", "Wisconsin"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `What pastry is used to make profittaroles?`,
    answer: "Choux",
    options: ["Filo", "Puff", "Choux", "Flaky"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `What is Felinology the study of?`,
    answer: "cats",
    options: ["oceans", "cats", "the lymph system and glands", "angels"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which of these brands has a bull on its logo?`,
    answer: "Lamborghini",
    options: ["Lamborghini", "Linux", "Hermès", "Tripadvisor"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
];

export const Animals: QuestionsInterface[] = [
  {
    question: `What is the largest land animal?`,
    answer: "Elephant",
    options: ["Elephant", "Giraffe", "Hippopotamus", "Rhinoceros"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `What is the fastest land animal?`,
    answer: "Cheetah",
    options: ["Cheetah", "Lion", "Gazelle", "Zebra"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `What is the smallest mammal in the world?`,
    answer: "Bat",
    options: ["Bat", "Mouse", "Shrew", "Hamster"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `What is the most venomous snake in the world?`,
    answer: "Inland taipan",
    options: ["Inland taipan", "Black mamba", "King cobra", "Rattlesnake"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `What is the only mammal capable of sustained flight?`,
    answer: "Bat",
    options: ["Bat", "Flying squirrel", "Pterodactyl", "Gliding possum"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `What animal is known as the 'king of the jungle'?`,
    answer: "Lion",
    options: ["Lion", "Tiger", "Elephant", "Gorilla"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `What is the only continent without native reptiles or snakes?`,
    answer: "Antarctica",
    options: ["Antarctica", "Australia", "South America", "Africa"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `What is the largest species of shark?`,
    answer: "Whale shark",
    options: [
      "Whale shark",
      "Great white shark",
      "Tiger shark",
      "Hammerhead shark",
    ],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `What is the largest bird in the world?`,
    answer: "Ostrich",
    options: ["Ostrich", "Eagle", "Albatross", "Condor"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `What is the fastest water animal?`,
    answer: "Sailfish",
    options: ["Sailfish", "Killer whale", "Dolphin", "Swordfish"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
];

export const History: QuestionsInterface[] = [
  {
    question: `Name the Shakespeare play from this plot summary: "Urged on by his wife, a man murders his king in order to take his place".?`,
    answer: "Macbeth",
    options: ["Macbeth", "Richard III", "Hamlet", "Romeo & Juliet"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A high school student is sent thirty years into the past in a time-traveling car.'?`,
    answer: "Back to the Future",
    options: [
      "The Truman Show",
      "Raiders of the Lost Ark",
      "Forrest Gump",
      "Back to the Future",
    ],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which American rhythm and blues girl group released the studio album 'Destiny Fulfilled'?`,
    answer: `Destiny's Child`,
    options: [
      `Destiny's Child`,
      "MercyMe",
      "Three 6 Mafia",
      "The Velvet Underground",
    ],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which English-American psychedelic rock band released the song 'Purple Haze'?`,
    answer: "The Jimi Hendrix Experience",
    options: [
      "The Jimi Hendrix Experience",
      "Poison",
      "The Pussycat Dolls",
      "Three 6 Mafia",
    ],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which author wrote 'Opticks, or a Treatise of the Reflections, Refractions, Inflections and Colours of Light'?`,
    answer: "Isaac Newton",
    options: [
      "Isaac Newton",
      "Daniel Defoe",
      "Percy Bysshe Shelley",
      "Walter Scott",
    ],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which King Wore Two Shirts At His Execution So As Not To Shiver And Appear Frightened?`,
    answer: "Charles I",
    options: ["Charles I", "Louis XIV", "Louis XVI", "Charles III"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which band includes 'Michael Cretu'?`,
    answer: "Enigma",
    options: ["Enigma", "Blue System", "Scorpions", "KMFDM"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Who Was Prime Minister When King Edward VIII Abdicated?`,
    answer: "Stanley Baldwin",
    options: [
      "Stanley Baldwin",
      "Anthony Eden",
      "Winston Churchill",
      "Bonar Law",
    ],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which of these is a baseball team based in Atlanta?`,
    answer: "Atlanta Braves",
    options: [
      "Atlanta Seahawks",
      "Atlanta Braves",
      "Atlanta Canadiens",
      "Atlanta Impact",
    ],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `In which country is singani a popular drink?`,
    answer: "Bolivia",
    options: ["Bolivia", "Ukraine", "China", "Belgium"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
];

export const PhilippineHistory: QuestionsInterface[] = [
  {
    question: `In which year was Martial Law declared in the Philippines?`,
    answer: "1972",
    options: ["1972", "1965", "1986", "2016"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `How old was Jose Rizal when he was executed?`,
    answer: "36",
    options: ["45", "50", "36", "28"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which of these isn’t a written work of Jose Rizal?`,
    answer: "Aves De Rapina",
    options: [
      "Aves De Rapina",
      "Mi Ultimo Adios",
      "El Filibusterismo",
      "Noli Me Tangere",
    ],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `In what year did the Philippine Revolution against Spain begin?`,
    answer: "1896",
    options: ["1896", "1901", "1890", "1861"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which of these wasn’t a President of the Philippines?`,
    answer: "Jose Abad Santos",
    options: [
      "Jose Abad Santos",
      "Carlos P Garcia",
      "Elpidio Quirino",
      "Manuel Roxas",
    ],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `In which year did Magellan discover the Philippines?`,
    answer: "1521",
    options: ["1521", "1571", "1600", "1611"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `On what date was Philippine Independence proclaimed?`,
    answer: "June 12, 1898",
    options: [
      "June 26, 1898",
      "June 12, 1898",
      "June 12, 1901",
      "July 4, 1898",
    ],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `What is the name of the script widely used in Luzon before the adaptation of the Latin Alphabet?`,
    answer: "Baybayin",
    options: ["Baybayin", "Cuneiform", "Tangut", "Nandinagari"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `In which year were the Gomburza priests executed?`,
    answer: "1872",
    options: ["1872", "1898", "1896", "1862"],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    question: `Which of these Filipino historical figures didn’t start a rebellion against Spain?`,
    answer: "Kapitan Tiago",
    options: [
      "Kapitan Tiago",
      "Diego Silang",
      "Francisco Dagohoy",
      "Andres Malong",
    ],
    status: "pending",
    isCorrect: false,
  },
];

export const categories: CategoryInterface[] = [
  {
    category: "Animals",
    questions: Animals,
  },
  {
    category: "International History",
    questions: History,
  },
  {
    category: "Philippine History",
    questions: PhilippineHistory,
  },
];
